<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Phiz Digital Content and Strategy </title><description>Sculpting the face of your company through words and images





</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.10</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:02:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Trust Phiz Digital</title><description>&lt;h3 id="socialmediaauditstrategyandbestpracticeguideforthequeenelizabethdiamondjubileetrust"&gt;Social Media Audit, Strategy and Best Practice Guide for The Queen Elizabeth Diamond Jubilee Trust&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After pitching for and winning the contract to conduct a social media audit, produce a strategy and deliver a best practice guide for the trust, we have now completed the first phase of the project.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/02/02/trust-phiz-digital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a63f25f8-19ad-47a9-868b-5d748ee63e0c</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:02:37 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/02/qedjt-logo-3.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;h3 id="socialmediaauditstrategyandbestpracticeguideforthequeenelizabethdiamondjubileetrust"&gt;Social Media Audit, Strategy and Best Practice Guide for The Queen Elizabeth Diamond Jubilee Trust&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/02/qedjt-logo-3.png" alt="Trust Phiz Digital"&gt;&lt;p&gt;After pitching for and winning the contract to conduct a social media audit, produce a strategy and deliver a best practice guide for the trust, we have now completed the first phase of the project.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Phiz Digital Infographics</title><description>Commission high quality infographics to use on a website, social media, POS asset or presentational aid. Suitable for business, retail or education.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/10/09/phiz-digital-infographics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2377abb6-43e6-4a86-9cda-75a1f7434543</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 18:49:27 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/10/s-vs-v-cover710.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;h3 id="phizdigitalcanprovideasinglebespokeinfographicoraseriesofpiecesasistheclientsrequirement"&gt;Phiz Digital can provide a single bespoke infographic or a series of pieces as is the clients requirement.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/10/s-vs-v-cover710.jpg" alt="Phiz Digital Infographics"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below is an infographic produced for VIP Electronic Cigarettes and Premium Vaping. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work compares the smoking traditional cigarettes to vaping by focusing on the absorption of nicotine and proved to be a valuable asset, informing and winning the confidence of customers - to date it has been viewed 4856 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/10/SmokingVsVaping-016.jpg" alt="Phiz Digital Infographics"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="whychooseinfographics"&gt;Why Choose Infographics?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Infographics represent a great form of digital content that is engaging and that can convey information in a manner that is easy to digest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They can also be a great way to help reinforce the branding of a company or product, using carefully crafted images, colours and copy to great effect - plus infographics can be used over and over because unlike written content there are no SEO issues in terms of duplicate content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, a high quality infographic adds another dimension to a website, blog or social media channel and makes for a refreshing change from the standard mix of photographs and text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Used in an educational setting, infographics are an effective learning resource that can really bring a topic to life. It's like providing learners with a snackable map of facts - yummy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="phizdigitalinfographics"&gt;Phiz Digital Infographics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to investigate the idea of investing in a bespoke infographic please &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/contact-us/" target="_blank"&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Lake District September Zeitgeist</title><description>Why digital content that is built using rich media is the key to engagement, good SEO and a quality user experience.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/09/21/lake-district-september-zeitgeist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">aa834257-6612-4b8f-b099-f06ed0c90b7a</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 12:25:42 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/drum-710.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/drum-710.jpg" alt="Lake District September Zeitgeist"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/drum-710-1.jpg" alt="Lake District September Zeitgeist"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="digitalcontentcontainingrichmediaisgoodforengagementseoandtheuserexperience"&gt;Digital content containing rich media is good for engagement, SEO and the user experience.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A zeitgeist for September 2017 in the Lake District. As the planet's most recently crowned UNESCO world heritage site, this autumn and winter should prove to be particularly interesting and this post, written for the Lakelovers blog attempts to capture all of the anticipated excitement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="whyhighqualitycontentmatters"&gt;Why High Quality Content Matters&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exceptional copywriting and some amazing images make for an interesting and informative piece of work. Engagement and the rewards that accompany it, is best achieved by featuring content that has been well thought through. In other words, expertly produced content, that sits in line with the interests and values of both the publisher and the intended audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While link building and SEO are important, featuring poorly written content that has been produced cheaply to serve them will not impress your clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog post reflects the ethos of the company and their mission to provide their customers with a comprehensive service, useful information and an amazing holiday experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lakelovers.co.uk/spotlight-on-september-in-the-lake-district/" target="_blank"&gt;Check out the article here and let us know what you think.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Phiz Digital&lt;/a&gt; X&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The Best Beaches in the Lake District</title><description>Phiz Digital provide high quality photography, digital content and strategy for business, retail and education. </description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/09/11/the-best-beaches-in-the-lake-district/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e4523322-9631-42f6-9cd9-d675993d9da4</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:34:11 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/Haverigg-Beach-460x385.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/Haverigg-Beach-460x385.jpg" alt="The Best Beaches in the Lake District"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/09/Haverigg-Beach-460x385-2.jpg" alt="The Best Beaches in the Lake District"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="littlebeknowntomanybutthelakedistrictishometomanyfinebeaches"&gt;Little beknown to many, but the Lake District is home to many fine beaches.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article was written for Lakelovers, posted on A Luxury Travel Blog and takes a look at the best beaches located in the planets latest world heritage site - the Lake District.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="photographyimagesourcingandediting"&gt;Photography, Image Sourcing and Editing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic images, whether they be state-of-the-art high resolution photographs or just well composed snaps are paramount when it comes to producing first class digital content. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You eat with your eyes and images, accompanied by written content, help us to formulate opinions and gesticulate our thoughts regarding the flavours we experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post prompted some excellent engagement and also serves as a testament to the diversity that the Lake District has to offer in terms of its landscape - defined by the use of images.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aluxurytravelblog.com/2017/08/22/5-of-the-best-beaches-in-the-lake-district/" target="_blank"&gt;See and read all about it here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="phizdigitalphotography"&gt;Phiz Digital Photography&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For high quality photography that will really make your website, blog or social media channels stand out from the crowd, &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/contact-us/" target="_blank"&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love Phiz Digital x&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Time for Great British Design</title><description>Using blog posts to improve engagement, conversion rates and expose the brand to the appropriate target audience.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/07/07/time-for-great-british-design/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ffb600d8-a1d3-4b84-aa00-073980bdc0e1</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 21:24:04 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/07/farer-gmt5-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/07/farer-gmt5-710-1.jpg" alt="Time for Great British Design"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/07/farer-gmt5-710.jpg" alt="Time for Great British Design"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a blog post for the Chapman Bags Journal, featuring Farer a luxury watch brand that are really making some waves at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chapmanbags.com/journal/time-for-a-new-bag/" target="_blank"&gt;Time for a New Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our brief from Chapman is to write a series of posts that will drive traffic to their website, help with conversions and expose the brand to a wider luxury demographic. Each post is keyword optimised and is delivered with images and advice on how to best promote it on the companies social channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the project moves forward, we will be writing guest blog posts for Chapman in order to get back links from like minded companies who are champions of British design and manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collaboration, mutual support and respect are paramount with this approach to digital marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many thanks &lt;a href="https://farer.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Farer&lt;/a&gt;  who have been welcoming, generous and kind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Phiz Digital&lt;/a&gt; X&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>News: Branching into Big Business</title><description>The recent acquisition of VIP Electronic Cigarette by BAT equals a new multinational client for Manchester start up company Phiz Digital.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/06/08/branching-into-big-business/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a0e6f24d-c1e0-42b6-8bd9-67b530dcc36e</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 21:04:26 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Vype-stufff710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Vype-stufff710-1.jpg" alt="News: Branching into Big Business"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Vype-stufff710.jpg" alt="News: Branching into Big Business"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have done a lot of work for VIP and they have recently become a subsidiary of &lt;a href="http://www.bat.com" target="_blank"&gt;British American Tobacco&lt;/a&gt; (BAT). This means we are now working, indirectly, for a multinational company. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our remit for &lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;VIP&lt;/a&gt; is basically to be their written voice and so all of their copywriting; web content, product descriptions etc are written by us - oh and we write and manage their &lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/blog" target="_blank"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, although we won't be working for BAT directly, we will be liaising with some of their staff and will need to adhere to the protocols of big business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love Phiz Digital X&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Blog Post: Bags &amp; Rifles</title><description>A blog post about the World Gunmakers Evening held in London on May 18 2017. The post was written by Phiz Digital for Chapman Bags, Cumbria.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/05/25/blog-post-bags-rifles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">494e7241-677d-4294-9f8b-e687201a48f7</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:25:07 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/guns-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/guns-710-1.jpg" alt="Blog Post: Bags &amp; Rifles"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/guns-710.jpg" alt="Blog Post: Bags &amp; Rifles"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog post covers the World Gunmakers Evening held in London, May 18 2017. The event attracts the elite from the world of field sports gun manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog was written for Chapman Bags who's heritage is in the production of accessories for the field sports niche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Handcrafted from their Cumbrian base and sold globally, this is a very high calibre brand and a fantastic business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copywriting for a high-end luggage brand who include model Marina Gibson, Michelin starred chef Kevin Tickle and travel journalist Tom Barber as their ambassadors is a real blast and we are aiming to do more work for Chapman Bags very soon.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read &lt;a href="http://www.chapmanbags.com/journal/shooting-for-success/" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Blog Post: Luxury Spas in the Lake District</title><description>A blog post produced by Phiz Digital that features some of the Lake Districts best luxury spas, their locations and the facilities on offer. </description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/04/07/blog-post-luxury-spas-in-the-lake-district/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a20008c6-c886-4d68-9a76-815df92d0aa4</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 20:53:18 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/spa-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/spa-710-1.jpg" alt="Blog Post: Luxury Spas in the Lake District"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/spa-710.jpg" alt="Blog Post: Luxury Spas in the Lake District"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written for Lakelovers and posted on &lt;a href="http://www.aluxurytravelblog.com/2017/04/07/top-5-spa-retreats-in-the-english-lake-district/" target="_blank"&gt;A Luxury Travel Blog&lt;/a&gt; this piece of work encapsulates what we love doing best - bringing together words and images.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Producing engaging content is such a pleasure when you have great material to work with and an exciting topic to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href="http://www.brimstonehotel.co.uk/brimstone-spa.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brimstone Spa&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://englishlakes.co.uk/hotels/lake-district-hotels/windermere-hotels/low-wood-bay/" target="_blank"&gt;Low Wood Bay Spa&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.applebymanor.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;Appleby Manor hotel and Garden Spa&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://thegilpin.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;Gilpin Lake House Jetty Spa and Spa Lodges&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.armathwaite-hall.com/?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=local" target="_blank"&gt;Armathwaite Hall Country House &amp;amp; Spa&lt;/a&gt; for all your help and guidance in putting this blog post together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We'd love to come and see you again soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com" target="_blank"&gt;Phiz Digital&lt;/a&gt; X&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Infographic: The Art of Sub Ohming</title><description>A high quality infographic used as an A3 POS asset for VIP retail outlets across the UK. The subject of which is sub ohm vaping devices and how they work.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/23/infographic-the-art-of-sub-ohming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">90f6ba4f-883a-4cd7-a655-645391ece42d</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 20:48:19 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/SubOhmCover-710.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/SubOhmCover-710.jpg" alt="Infographic: The Art of Sub Ohming"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/03/SubOhm-jpeg.jpg" alt="Infographic: The Art of Sub Ohming"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another fantastic infographic piece for a high ranking website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This version of the piece is for an A3 POS asset that will be used in VIP retail outlets across the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people who buy sub ohm vaping devices happily use them without knowing anything about how they work or the emerging subculture that have embraced them. The purpose of this infographic is to inform and to raise awareness of both those things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More superb graphics from Rik Cheetham - using just 2 colours gives the piece drama, cool aesthetics and clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's a link to the original blog post:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/blog/13/The-Art-of-Sub-Ohming" target="_blank"&gt;The Art of Sub Ohming&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Photoshop: Glorious Food</title><description>Phiz Digital know the power of strong imagery and have loved working with luxury restaurants in the Lake District to showcase the very best of the region</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/14/photoshop-glorious-food/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ae2dcac5-2088-45af-9d1c-6467c8beac2b</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 21:20:54 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/glorious-food-710.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/glorious-food-710.jpg" alt="Photoshop: Glorious Food"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/glorious-food-710.jpg" alt="Photoshop: Glorious Food"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We're loving sourcing and working with some beautiful photography from some of the best restaurants and gastro-pubs in the Lake District. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Produced by Phiz Digital for Lakelovers and published on &lt;a href="http://www.aluxurytravelblog.com/2017/03/14/5-of-the-best-restaurants-in-the-lake-district/" target="_blank"&gt;A Luxury Travel Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to; &lt;a href="http://www.wildsmithhotels.com" target="_blank"&gt;Wildsmith Hotels&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.style-trunk.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;Style Trunk&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.thecommunicationsstore.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;The Communications Store&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.holbeckghyll.com" target="_blank"&gt;Holbeck Ghyll&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.oldstamphouse.com" target="_blank"&gt;The Old Stamp House&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.lenclume.co.uk" target="_blank"&gt;L'Enclume&lt;/a&gt; for all your help. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Blog Post: The Golden Fleece of the North</title><description>Blog post about the beauty of the Northern Lake District. The blog focuses on Keswick and the reasons to visit it.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/10/blog-post-the-golden-fleece-of-the-north-lakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4870e3e3-9dc6-4a35-b0bb-a36677050f43</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 22:00:45 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Derwent-Water-Boats-710-1.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Derwent-Water-Boats-710-1.png" alt="Blog Post: The Golden Fleece of the North"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Derwent-Water-Boats-710.png" alt="Blog Post: The Golden Fleece of the North"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a copywriting brief to deliver an uplifting post for the Lakelovers Blog following the devastation of &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xu28gPfAFPc" target="_blank"&gt;Storm Desmond&lt;/a&gt; and the floods that followed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, the client had not long since opened their Northern office in Keswick, which was looking for some positive PR also. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During that week, from the 3rd-8th December 2016, Lakelovers, the longest established self-catering cottage holiday agency in the Lake District, were keen to remind folk of the beauty of Ullswater and the North Lake District. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we are Lovers of the Lakes ourselves, we were very happy to help! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We only need to look at photography of the region to be reminded of why famous artists like Beatrix Potter, William Wordsworth and Wainright were mesmerised by the unrivalled beauty and poetic charm of this quiet part of the the English Lakes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, knowing the warmth of the North Lake's community and all that this area has to offer, it was a pleasure to write this blog post. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lakelovers.co.uk/why-the-north-lakes-has-it-all" target="_blank"&gt;Why The North Lakes Has It All&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Phiz Digital: Just a Click Away</title><description>Phiz Digital launch a website to promote their services | Content Writing | Infographics | Photography | SEO | Social Media | Illustration | copywriting |</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/09/phiz-digital-just-a-click-away/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6a4e6454-8ef9-4e76-bcb7-ea1b475b0f3f</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 22:32:57 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Graysons-PhizEd-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;h3 id="phizdigitallaunchnewwebsite"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phiz Digital Launch New Website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Graysons-PhizEd-710-1.jpg" alt="Phiz Digital: Just a Click Away"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/Graysons-PhizEd-710.jpg" alt="Phiz Digital: Just a Click Away"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manchester UK, March 2017 – &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com" target="_blank"&gt;Phiz Digital&lt;/a&gt; a company specialising in the production of digital content for businesses, have launched a website to promote their services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website is elegant, it features photographs taken by the company directors four year old son, has a monochrome theme and cost absolutely nothing to build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’ve been setting the foundation stones of the company for some time now and the site will play a pivotal role in its development moving forward. Building the site has been a real family affair, my son Grayson took the photographs used on the site, I produced the copy and my brother-in-law Chris was responsible for the coding wizardry” Paul Whittland, Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site itself is very simple, featuring just five pages it feels like a website/blog hybrid, there’s an almost ghostly art-house feel to it and there are no gimmicks or pop ups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks aside, the site contains some interesting information, the &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/client/" target="_blank"&gt;Clients and Friends&lt;/a&gt; page lists the companies that Phiz are currently working with. Luxury brands are who Phiz Digital specialise in helping - Chapman make luxury bags and are champions of the made in Briton ethos, while VIP is one of the biggest suppliers of premium vaping products and e-liquid in the UK and overseas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’re really happy with the clients we are working with and for the moment we are at capacity in terms of workload which is great. We will soon be making provision for more clients, but our primary objective is to make sure our current clients have everything they need” Louise Whittland, Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phiz Digital’s business plan for the next 12 months involves winning more clients and taking on more staff to accommodate this expansion.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The site really encapsulates the company and its ethos, it’s simple, honest and great to get involved with.” Louise Whittland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com" target="_blank"&gt;phizdigital.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Infographic: The Truth About Nicotine</title><description>An infographic produced for VIP, containing images and copy relating to nicotine facts, statistics and figures. Credits: VIP Paul Whittland and Rik Cheetham</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/02/the-truth-about-nicotine-infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">88e66e91-a803-4718-ac4c-e218b5d7beab</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 21:54:35 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/ttan_cover_Image710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/ttan_cover_Image710-1.jpg" alt="Infographic: The Truth About Nicotine"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/ttan_cover_Image710.jpg" alt="Infographic: The Truth About Nicotine"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A brilliant piece of design work from Rik Cheetham for the VIP blog. The post examines the effects of nicotine of the human body and on the environment. It also highlights some of the differences between smoking and vaping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the second infographic project that Rik and I have collaborated on and our burgeoning alliance is getting more interesting and fruitful by the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the link below to see the work, a full transcript and a quiz we added to the post using Apester. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/blog/29/the-truth-about-nicotine" target="_blank"&gt;The Truth About Nicotine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>VIP and Innokin Team Up</title><description>Press release | Phiz Digital explain how to create a strong press release strategy and why it's vital that business' use good copywriters to produce them. </description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/24/vip-and-innokin-link-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a03ab455-4b36-43a5-82ba-5bce6705d75b</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 10:58:03 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/cool-fire-iv-tc-100w-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/cool-fire-iv-tc-100w-710-1.jpg" alt="VIP and Innokin Team Up"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why a Press Release is Still a Valuable Tool&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/cool-fire-iv-tc-100w-710.jpg" alt="VIP and Innokin Team Up"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's always great to feel like you're part of the action and writing a simple press release about VIP's link up with Innokin was a cool way to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breaking news is always exciting, especially when the news is good news and I was pleased to hear that VIP had won another feather for their cap - they had just secured a partnership with Innokin, an acclaimed vaping product manufacturer.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as being fun, this brief also reinforced the idea that a good press release still carries weight. Here's a taste of what the press release said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;a href="http://www.innokin.com/vaporizers/cool-fire-iv-tc-100/" target="_blank"&gt;Cool Fire IV TC 100W&lt;/a&gt; is really pushing the boundaries of vaping style and technology. This vaporiser looks great and it has the power to match its looks, not only that, Innokin have used a 3300mAh battery, which is compact, but will also last all day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The TC 100 may not be a 200W mega beast used by the ultra hip of the vaping community, those who aspire to blow the perfect "jellyfish" and visit vaping conventions, but it doesn't have to be. This device is aimed at a different type of client, one who's enjoyment of vaping is maybe a little less gregarious and one who just enjoys quality vaping.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of a press release is to keep the media and the public up to date with news about your company. There is ongoing speculation about the death of the press release, but there are several reasons why this is simply never going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First&lt;/strong&gt;, a press release, written well, is an affordable way of getting information to the media quickly. A press release should take no more than an hour to write and then seconds to distribute - to do this all you need is a list of press contacts or to employ the services of a press release distribution company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second&lt;/strong&gt;, a press release strategy that has regular frequency built in can build trust amongst customers, shareholders and partners. Plus a good press release is like a birthday present to a journalist or editor because the majority of the work is done for them, all they have to do is rewrite the story and publish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third&lt;/strong&gt;, press releases are good for business, sharing good news attracts customers and also investors. Show that your business is a successful one that carries good momentum and people will start to wonder why and then investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The press release - dead? Au contraire, it's a cheap, easy and effective marketing tool that is very much alive, well and helping companies thrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your company has an important announcement to make and would like to spread the word with a press release, then Phiz Digital can help you. For more information &lt;a href="http://phizdigital.com/contact-us/" target="_blank"&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Victory at Doncaster</title><description>Content writing | A blog piece about Phiz Digital covering Doncaster races for VIP. Phiz Digital produced a news piece, video bytes and a video interview.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/13/victory-at-doncaster-races/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2dcb0855-5f49-458b-88a6-d800d9285ff7</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 09:18:36 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/vip-races-710-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/vip-races-710-1.jpg" alt="Victory at Doncaster"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/06/vip-races-710.jpg" alt="Victory at Doncaster"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day out at the races with VIP Premium Vaping and E-Liquids, turned out to be much more than I expected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brief was to write a news piece covering VIP's sponsorship of the event, but it wasn't long before I was coordinating video bytes, interviewing winning jockeys (on camera) and sitting down to a fabulous lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived at the racecourse at around 9.30am and after acquainting myself with the geography, I got stuck into making some notes about the general atmosphere and the various features VIP had contributed to the proceedings. These included a VW camper van with a VIP spray job, a giant video game and a rather cool vaping lounge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the vaping lounge that I headed to for respite from the heat, at trackside it was 21° C and it was only 10.30am. After a few minutes with my Skystorm AM30, I decided to find the press office, just in case I needed wifi later in the day and sure enough, free wifi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the clock crept towards lunchtime, I made my way to the Lincoln Restaurant where Louise Stamper, CCO at VIP, had kindly invited me and several others to join her for lunch. Fantastic food and chilled champagne in the company of fine folk, such as Tracey Tennison from Nexus Engage, Marc Rayton, who works at Space and People and Cal Moores from VIP - Cal acted as my valiant sidekick for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/VIP-Docaster-Lunch.jpg" alt="Victory at Doncaster" title=""&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lunch over and it was time for the races to begin. The first race was won by a beautiful looking horse called Lost at Sea. By 3pm it was time for the VIP sponsored race, the highlight of the day and I had been asked to try to grab the winning jockey for a quick interview - post race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/Winning-VIP-Horse.jpg" alt="Victory at Doncaster"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The VIP Premium Vaping and E-Liquids Scarbrough Stakes, was a 5-furlong race with a competitive lineup. Priceless romped home to a stonking victory and after jockey Sylvestre De Sousa had finished his official media duties, he was kind enough to answer some of my questions - never in a million years did I think I would interviewing a winning jockey at the Doncaster St. Ledger Festival!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, back to the vaping lounge and my Skystorm. Along the way I bump into several race goers, who are more than happy to provide me with a little extra for the client, some video bytes, shot on my iPhone and gratefully received - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/vipcig/status/773571599400333312" target="_blank"&gt;you and me VIP!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a little more champagne, the day started to draw to an end and it was time to reflect on all that had happened. Not only had VIP been wonderful sponsors, they had also been wonderful hosts and it's not hard to see why this company are leading the way, not only in supplying premium quality vaping products, but in experiential marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To read the news article, click on the link:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/news/post/vip-victory-at-doncaster-races" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/news/post/vip-victory-at-doncaster-races&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>