<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Phiz Digital</title><description>Sculpting the face of your company through words and images





</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.10</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 21:15:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>The Truth About Nicotine - Infographic</title><description>An infographic produced for VIP, containing images and copy relating to nicotine facts, statistics and figures. Credits: VIP and Rik Cheetham</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/02/the-truth-about-nicotine-infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">88e66e91-a803-4718-ac4c-e218b5d7beab</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 21:54:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/03/ttav_cover_Image450-1.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A brilliant piece of design work from RiK Cheetham for the VIP blog. The post examines the effects of nicotine of the human body and on the environment. It also highlights some of the differences between smoking and vaping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the second infographic project that Rik and I have collaborated on and our burgeoning alliance is getting more interesting and fruitful by the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the link below to see the work, a full transcript and a quiz we added to the post using Apester. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/blog/29/the-truth-about-nicotine" target="_blank"&gt;The Truth About Nicotine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>VIP and Innokin Team Up</title><description>Press release | Phiz Digital explain how to create a strong press release strategy and why it's vital that business' use good copywriters to write them. </description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/24/vip-and-innokin-link-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a03ab455-4b36-43a5-82ba-5bce6705d75b</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 10:58:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why a Press Release is Still a Valuable Tool:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/Cool-Fire-IV-TC-100W.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's always great to feel like you're part of the action and writing this simple &lt;a href="https://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/news/post/vip-e-cigarettes-link-up-with-innokin" target="_blank"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; about VIP's link up with Innokin was a cool way to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breaking news is always exciting, especially when the news is good news and I was pleased to hear that VIP had won another feather for their cap. For me this brief also, reinforced the idea that a good press release still carries weight. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="http://www.innokin.com/vaporizers/cool-fire-iv-tc-100/" target="_blank"&gt;Cool Fire IV TC 100W&lt;/a&gt; is really pushing the boundaries of vaping style and technology. This vaporiser looks great and it has the power to match its looks, not only that, Innokin have used a 3300mAh battery, which is compact, but will also last all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TC 100 may not be a 200W mega beast used by the ultra hip of the vaping community, those who aspire to blow the perfect "jellyfish" and visit vaping conventions, but it doesn't have to be. This device is aimed at a different type of client, one who's enjoyment of vaping is maybe a little less gregarious and one who just enjoys quality vaping. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of a press release is to keep the media and the public up to date with news about your company. There is ongoing speculation about the death of the press release, but there are several reasons why this is simply never going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, a press release, written well, is an affordable way of getting information to the media quickly. A press release should take no more than an hour to write and then seconds to distribute - to do this all you need is a list of press contacts. If, of course, you want then to post the release online, distribution will take a little longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, a press release strategy that has regular frequency built in can build trust amongst journalists who are then more likely to publish the release and comment on it. A good press release is like a birthday present to a journalist or editor because the majority of the work is done for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, press releases are good for business, sharing good news attracts customers and also investors. Show that your business is a successful one that carries good momentum and people will start to wonder why and then investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The press release - dead? Au contraire, it's a cheap, easy and effective marketing tool that is very much alive, well and helping companies thrive.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Victory at Doncaster</title><description>Content writing | A blog piece about Phiz Digital covering Doncaster races for VIP. Phiz Digital produced a news piece, video bytes and a video interview.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/13/victory-at-doncaster-races/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2dcb0855-5f49-458b-88a6-d800d9285ff7</guid><dc:creator>Paul Whittland</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 09:18:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/VIP-Races-2.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day out at the races with VIP Electronic Vaping Devices and E-Liquids, turned out to be much more than I expected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brief was to write a news piece covering VIP's sponsorship of the event, but it wasn't long before I was coordinating video bytes, interviewing winning jockeys (on camera) and sitting down to a fabulous lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived at the racecourse at around 9.30am and after acquainting myself with the geography, I got stuck into making some notes about the general atmosphere and the various features VIP had contributed to the proceedings. These included a VW camper van with a VIP spray job, a giant video game and a rather cool vaping lounge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the vaping lounge that I headed to for respite from the heat, at trackside it was 21° C and it was only 10.30am. After a few minutes with my Skystorm AM30, I decided to find the press office, just in case I needed wifi later in the day and sure enough, free wifi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the clock crept towards lunchtime, I made my way to the Lincoln Restaurant where Louise Stamper, CCO at VIP, had kindly invited me and several others to join her for lunch. Fantastic food and chilled champagne in the company of fine folk, such as Tracey Tennison from Nexus Engage, Marc Rayton, who works at Space and People and Cal Moores from VIP - Cal acted as my valiant sidekick for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/VIP-Docaster-Lunch.jpg" alt="" title=""&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lunch over and it was time for the races to begin. The first race was won by a beautiful looking horse called Lost at Sea. By 3pm it was time for the VIP sponsored race, the highlight of the day and I had been asked to try to grab the winning jockey for a quick interview - post race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2016/09/Winning-VIP-Horse.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The VIP Premium Vaping and E-Liquids Scarbrough Stakes, was a 5-furlong race with a competitive lineup. Priceless romped home to a stonking victory and after jockey Sylvestre De Sousa had finished his official media duties, he was kind enough to answer some of my questions - never in a million years did I think I would interviewing a winning jockey at the Doncaster St. Ledger Festival!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, back to the vaping lounge and my Skystorm. Along the way I bump into several race goers, who are more than happy to provide me with a little extra for the client, some video bytes, shot on my iPhone and gratefully received - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/vipcig/status/773571599400333312" target="_blank"&gt;you and me VIP!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a little more champagne, the day started to draw to an end and it was time to reflect on all that had happened. Not only had VIP been wonderful sponsors, they had also been wonderful hosts and it's not hard to see why this company are leading the way, not only in supplying premium quality vaping products, but in experiential marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To read the news article, click on the link:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/news/post/vip-victory-at-doncaster-races" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vipelectroniccigarette.co.uk/news/post/vip-victory-at-doncaster-races&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>